let questions = [
  {
    "number": 1,
    "question": "config",
    "answer": "設定",
    "options": ["設定", "報酬", "衣類", "開くこと"],
　　"part": "noun"
  },
{    "number": 2,    "question": "immediate",   "answer": "即時の",    "options": ["晴れた", "即時の", "個人の", "入手できる"]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 3,    "question": "pursue",    "answer": "追及する",    "options": ["旅行する", "引き起こす", "投資する", "追及する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 4,    "question": "inform",    "answer": "知らせる",    "options": ["購入する", "満足させる", "取り戻す", "知らせる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 5,    "question": "anyway",    "answer": "とにかく",    "options": ["最近", "相対的に", "とにかく", "おそらく"]  ,"part": "adverb"},
{    "number": 6,    "question": "degree",    "answer": "学位",    "options": ["伝統", "学位", "量", "結果"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 7,    "question": "benefit",    "answer": "利益を得る",    "options": ["利益を得る", "出荷する", "取り除く", "餌を与える"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 8,    "question": "replace",    "answer": "取り替える",    "options": ["更新する", "拒む", "取り替える", "比較する"] ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 9,    "question": "infer",    "answer": "推察する",    "options": ["もてなす", "応募する", "推察する", "見て回る"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 10,    "question": "following",    "answer": "次の",    "options": ["晴れた", "次の", "即時の", "喜んで"]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 11,    "question": "accomplish",    "answer": "成し遂げる",    "options": ["告白する", "に気づく", "卒業する", "成し遂げる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 12,    "question": "reinforce",    "answer": "強化する",    "options": ["分析する", "充電する", "強化する", "出席する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 13,    "question": "demand",    "answer": "要求する",    "options": ["要求する", "模倣する", "推薦する", "確保する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 14,    "question": "refer",    "answer": "参照する",    "options": ["郵送する", "参照する", "含む", "変える"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 15,    "question": "booking",    "answer": "予約",    "options": ["予約", "支払い", "配達", "決定"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 16,    "question": "simulate",    "answer": "模倣する",    "options": ["異議を唱える", "餌を与える", "応募する", "模倣する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 17,    "question": "cause",    "answer": "引き起こす",    "options": ["おわびをする", "引き起こす", "応募する", "奮闘する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 18,    "question": "available",    "answer": "入手できる",    "options": ["気前のよい", "喜んで", "次の", "入手できる"]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 19,    "question": "commercial",    "answer": "商業の",    "options": ["地元の", "商業の", "個人の", "入手できる"]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 20,    "question": "occupy",    "answer": "占有する",    "options": ["資金を与える", "占有する", "再開する", "維持する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 21,    "question": "compare",    "answer": "比較する",    "options": ["参照する", "更新する", "積み重ねる", "比較する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 22,    "question": "inquire",    "answer": "尋ねる",    "options": ["強化する", "稼ぐ", "知らせる", "尋ねる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 23,    "question": "department",    "answer": "売り場",    "options": ["建設", "商品", "開くこと", "売り場"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 24,    "question": "describe",    "answer": "説明する",    "options": ["修正する", "予期する", "説明する", "現れる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 25,    "question": "remove",    "answer": "取り除く",    "options": ["取り除く", "確認する", "検討する", "空にする"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 26,    "question": "conference",    "answer": "会議",    "options": ["設定", "関係", "会議", "感心"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 27,    "question": "decision",    "answer": "決定",    "options": ["労働力", "決定", "注意", "予約"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 28,    "question": "introduce",    "answer": "紹介する",    "options": ["指示する", "みなす", "紹介する", "出発する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 29,    "question": "reject",    "answer": "却下する",    "options": ["却下する", "推薦する", "制定する", "輸入する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 30,    "question": "destroy",    "answer": "破壊する",    "options": ["導く", "推察する", "示す", "破壊する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 31,    "question": "income",    "answer": "収入",    "options": ["収入", "費用", "施設", "善意の行為"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 32,    "question": "empty",    "answer": "空にする",    "options": ["空にする", "ゆるめる", "除く", "却下する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 33,    "question": "entertain",    "answer": "もてなす",    "options": ["含む", "移す", "向ける", "もてなす"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 34,    "question": "likely",    "answer": "おそらく",    "options": ["おそらく", "正しく", "最近", "過程"]  ,"part": "adverb"},
{    "number": 35,    "question": "establish",    "answer": "設立する",    "options": ["設立する", "詳しく調べる", "集中させる", "接続する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 36,    "question": "star	　　　",    "answer": "主演する",    "options": ["通勤する", "要求する", "変える", "主演する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 37,    "question": "secure",    "answer": "確保する",    "options": ["輸入する", "を取り替える", "確保する", "解雇する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 38,    "question": "state",    "answer": "述べる",    "options": ["割り当てる", "述べる", "注ぐ", "拒む"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 39,    "question": "equipment",    "answer": "機器",    "options": ["詳細", "報酬", "設定", "機器"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 40,    "question": "basis",    "answer": "基準",    "options": ["研究", "基準", "印象", "量"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 41,    "question": "suffer",    "answer": "被る",    "options": ["許す", "被る", "尋ねる", "主催する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 42,    "question": "environmental",    "answer": "環境の",    "options": ["定期的に", "商業の", "金銭上の", "環境の"]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 43,    "question": "apologize",    "answer": "おわびをする",    "options": ["紹介する", "実演する", "見逃す", "おわびをする"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 44,    "question": "provide",    "answer": "提供する",    "options": ["餌を与える", "代表する", "提供する", "告白する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 45,    "question": "browse",    "answer": "見て回る",    "options": ["修理する", "集まる", "運ぶ", "見て回る"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 46,    "question": "tradition",    "answer": "伝統",    "options": ["伝統", "生産", "会社", "活動"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 47,    "question": "satisfy",    "answer": "満足させる",    "options": ["占有する", "現れる", "投資する", "満足させる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 48,    "question": "local",    "answer": "地元の",    "options": ["地元の", "定期的に", "年に1度の", "気前のよい"]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 49,    "question": "facility",    "answer": "施設",    "options": ["売り場", "衣類", "施設", "空き室"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 50,    "question": "institute",    "answer": "制定する",    "options": ["出席する", "制定する", "成し遂げる", "資金を与える"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 51,    "question": "resume",    "answer": "再開する",    "options": ["のせいにする", "示す", "再開する", "の方を好む"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 52,    "question": "opening",    "answer": "開くこと",    "options": ["善意の行為", "集まり", "手に入ること", "開くこと"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 53,    "question": "notify",    "answer": "知らせる",    "options": ["取り戻す", "追及する", "知らせる", "述べる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 54,    "question": "maintain",    "answer": "維持する",    "options": ["維持する", "増える", "提示する", "延期する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 55,    "question": "host	",    "answer": "主催する",    "options": ["告白する", "掃く", "投資する", "主催する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 56,    "question": "construction",    "answer": "建設",    "options": ["活動", "会議", "建設", "候補者"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 57,    "question": "notice　　　",    "answer": "気づく",    "options": ["気づく", "被る", "掃く", "見逃す"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 58,    "question": "instruct",    "answer": "指示する",    "options": ["成し遂げる", "雇う", "指示する", "推薦する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 59,    "question": "deliver",    "answer": "届ける",    "options": ["届ける", "出発する", "貢献する", "設立する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 60,    "question": "participate",    "answer": "参加する",    "options": ["集まる", "みなす", "参加する", "挨拶する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 61,    "question": "tour	",    "answer": "旅行する",    "options": ["旅行する", "提示する", "分析する", "述べる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 62,    "question": "subscribe",    "answer": "購読する",    "options": ["旅行する", "検討する", "申し出る", "代表する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 63,    "question": "correct",    "answer": "修正する",    "options": ["空にする", "参照する", "修正する", "利益を得る"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 64,    "question": "merchandise",    "answer": "商品",    "options": ["機器", "利益", "社員", "商品"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 65,    "question": "loosen",    "answer": "ゆるめる",    "options": ["除く", "実現する", "占有する", "ゆるめる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 66,    "question": "research",    "answer": "研究",    "options": ["研究", "代理店", "収入", "成長"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 67,    "question": "focus",    "answer": "集中させる",    "options": ["強化する", "往復運転で運ぶ", "もうかる", "集中させる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 68,    "question": "result",    "answer": "結果",    "options": ["結果", "設定", "決定", "生産"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 69,    "question": "mail",    "answer": "郵送する",    "options": ["郵送する", "購入する", "含む", "餌を与える"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 70,    "question": "attend",    "answer": "出席する",    "options": ["の方を好む", "出席する", "奮闘する", "提示する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 71,    "question": "fine",    "answer": "晴れた",    "options": ["晴れた", "喜んで", "模倣する", "入手できる"]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 72,    "question": "shift",    "answer": "移す",    "options": ["移す", "却下する", "掃く", "卒業する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 73,    "question": "admiration",    "answer": "感心",    "options": ["業績", "科目", "感心", "調査"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 74,    "question": "gather",    "answer": "集まる",    "options": ["引き起こす", "集まる", "示す", "向ける"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 75,    "question": "delivery",    "answer": "配達",    "options": ["配達", "節約", "代理店", "支払い"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 76,    "question": "availability",    "answer": "手に入ること",    "options": ["感心", "集まり", "労働", "手に入ること"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 77,    "question": "announce",    "answer": "発表する",    "options": ["提案する", "注ぐ", "述べる", "発表する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 78,    "question": "recently",    "answer": "最近",    "options": ["最近", "現在は", "とにかく", "正しく"]  ,"part": "adverb"},
{    "number": 79,    "question": "regularly",    "answer": "定期的に",    "options": ["年に1度の", "定期的に", "即時の", ""]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 80,    "question": "blame",    "answer": "のせいにする",    "options": ["紹介する", "解雇する", "議論する", "のせいにする"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 81,    "question": "workforce",    "answer": "労働力",    "options": ["顧客", "経営", "報酬", "労働力"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 82,    "question": "require",    "answer": "要求する",    "options": ["予期する", "通勤する", "要求する", "延期する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 83,    "question": "indicate",    "answer": "示す",    "options": ["運ぶ", "尋ねる", "認める", "示す"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 84,    "question": "impression",    "answer": "印象",    "options": ["印象", "基準", "労働", "候補者"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 85,    "question": "struggle",    "answer": "奮闘する",    "options": ["推察する", "強化する", "実演する", "奮闘する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 86,    "question": "employee",    "answer": "社員",    "options": ["実験", "調査", "社員", "応募"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 87,    "question": "fund",    "answer": "資金を与える",    "options": ["資金を与える", "雇う", "増える", "充電する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 88,    "question": "additional",    "answer": "付加的な",    "options": ["個人の", "次の", "付加的な", "金銭上の"]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 89,    "question": "shuttle",    "answer": "往復運転で運ぶ",    "options": ["確認する", "更新する", "貢献する", "往復運転で運ぶ"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 90,    "question": "depart",    "answer": "出発する",    "options": ["設立する", "所有する", "提供する", "出発する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 91,    "question": "sweep",    "answer": "掃く",    "options": ["掃く", "交換する", "従う", "導く"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 92,    "question": "review",    "answer": "検討する",    "options": ["検討する", "説明する", "導く", "代表する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 93,    "question": "appear",    "answer": "現れる",    "options": ["主演する", "提案する", "現れる", "出荷する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 94,    "question": "offer",    "answer": "申し出る",    "options": ["申し出る", "許す", "再開する", "もうかる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 95,    "question": "load",    "answer": "荷物を積む",    "options": ["郵送する", "利益を得る", "充電する", "荷物を積む"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 96,    "question": "production",    "answer": "生産",    "options": ["実験", "収入", "節約", "生産"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 97,    "question": "favor",    "answer": "善意の行為",    "options": ["基準", "応募", "賞", "善意の行為"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 98,    "question": "earn	",    "answer": "稼ぐ",    "options": ["接続する", "稼ぐ", "ひきつける", "認める"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 99,    "question": "fire",    "answer": "解雇する",    "options": ["雇う", "ひきつける", "おわびをする", "解雇する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 100,    "question": "process",    "answer": "過程",    "options": ["印象", "過程", "予約", "経営"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 101,    "question": "apply",    "answer": "応募する",    "options": ["応募する", "模倣する", "おわびをする", "異議を唱える"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 102,    "question": "analyze",    "answer": "分析する",    "options": ["比較する", "分析する", "見て回る", "を取り替える"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 103,    "question": "commute",    "answer": "通勤する",    "options": ["被る", "積み重ねる", "延期する", "通勤する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 104,    "question": "generous",    "answer": "気前のよい",    "options": ["商業の", "入手できる", "喜んで", "気前のよい"]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 105,    "question": "import",    "answer": "輸入する",    "options": ["届ける", "卒業する", "検討する", "輸入する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 106,    "question": "detail",    "answer": "詳細",    "options": ["調査", "詳細", "予約", "空き室"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 107,    "question": "attain",    "answer": "実現する",    "options": ["記録する", "実現する", "説明する", "挨拶する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 108,    "question": "direct",    "answer": "向ける",    "options": ["向ける", "取り除く", "気づく", "詳しく調べる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 109,    "question": "relationship",    "answer": "関係",    "options": ["手に入ること", "集まり", "伝統", "関係"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 110,    "question": "repair",    "answer": "修理する",    "options": ["修理する", "ゆるめる", "運ぶ", "要求する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 111,    "question": "recover",    "answer": "取り戻す",    "options": ["見逃す", "集中させる", "取り戻す", "予定を変更する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 112,    "question": "contribution",    "answer": "貢献",    "options": ["展示", "貢献", "会議", "契約"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 113,    "question": "confess",    "answer": "告白する",    "options": ["旅行する", "ゆるめる", "推察する", "告白する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 114,    "question": "increase",    "answer": "増える",    "options": ["増える", "届ける", "満足させる", "所有する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 115,    "question": "growth",    "answer": "成長",    "options": ["開くこと", "施設", "成長", "衣類"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 116,    "question": "update",    "answer": "更新する",    "options": ["強化する", "要求する", "充電する", "更新する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 117,    "question": "quantity",    "answer": "量",    "options": ["量", "支払い", "建設", "配達"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 118,    "question": "regard",    "answer": "みなす",    "options": ["挨拶する", "みなす", "制定する", "修理する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 119,    "question": "include",    "answer": "含む",    "options": ["含む", "移す", "出荷する", "維持する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 120,    "question": "cost",    "answer": "費用",    "options": ["費用", "展示", "売り場", "手に入ること"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 121,    "question": "greet",    "answer": "挨拶する",    "options": ["挨拶する", "出荷する", "紹介する", "記録する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 122,    "question": "consider",    "answer": "検討する",    "options": ["追及する", "指示する", "検討する", "提案する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 123,    "question": "currently",    "answer": "現在は",    "options": ["定期的に", "相対的に", "最近", "現在は"]  ,"part": "adverb"},
{    "number": 124,    "question": "activity",    "answer": "活動",    "options": ["業績", "会社", "印象", "活動"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 125,    "question": "refuse",    "answer": "拒む",    "options": ["拒む", "従う", "購入する", "ゆるめる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 126,    "question": "subject",    "answer": "科目",    "options": ["科目", "予算", "学位", "候補者"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 127,    "question": "assign",    "answer": "割り当てる",    "options": ["提供する", "割り当てる", "代表する", "主催する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 128,    "question": "advertising",    "answer": "広告",    "options": ["機器", "業績", "貢献", "広告"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 129,    "question": "vacancy",    "answer": "空き室",    "options": ["経営", "貢献", "予算", "空き室"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 130,    "question": "correctly",    "answer": "正しく",    "options": ["正しく", "おそらく", "現在は", "相対的に"]  ,"part": "adverb"},
{    "number": 131,    "question": "stack",    "answer": "積み重ねる",    "options": ["充電する", "破壊する", "奮闘する", "積み重ねる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 132,    "question": "expect",    "answer": "予期する",    "options": ["卒業する", "引き起こす", "予期する", "予定を変更する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 133,    "question": "connect",    "answer": "接続する",    "options": ["知らせる", "輸入する", "接続する", "所有する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 134,    "question": "saving",    "answer": "節約",    "options": ["節約", "報酬", "経営", "展示物"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 135,    "question": "firm",    "answer": "会社",    "options": ["関係", "会社", "基準", "代理店"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 136,    "question": "attract",    "answer": "ひきつける",    "options": ["気づく", "取り替える", "ひきつける", "告白する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 137,    "question": "pour",    "answer": "注ぐ",    "options": ["ゆるめる", "注ぐ", "実行する", "のせいにする"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 138,    "question": "profit",    "answer": "利益",    "options": ["賞", "広告", "利益", "労働力"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 139,    "question": "client",    "answer": "顧客",    "options": ["契約", "顧客", "生産", "衣類"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 140,    "question": "attention",    "answer": "注意",    "options": ["空き室", "会社", "研究", "注意"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 141,    "question": "feed",    "answer": "餌を与える",    "options": ["要求する", "もてなす", "雇う", "餌を与える"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 142,    "question": "present",    "answer": "提示する",    "options": ["詳しく調べる", "現れる", "提示する", "被る"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 143,    "question": "annual",    "answer": "年に1度の",    "options": ["次の", "環境の", "地元の", "年に1度の"]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 144,    "question": "labor",    "answer": "労働",    "options": ["賞", "貢献", "労働", "感心"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 145,    "question": "explain",    "answer": "説明する",    "options": ["挨拶する", "修正する", "説明する", "要求する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 146,    "question": "experiment",    "answer": "実験",    "options": ["実験", "建設", "成長", "顧客"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 147,    "question": "payment",    "answer": "支払い",    "options": ["支払い", "印象", "詳細", "利益"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 148,    "question": "relatively",    "answer": "相対的に",    "options": ["とにかく", "相対的に", "おそらく", "最近"]  ,"part": "adverb"},
{    "number": 149,    "question": "recognize",    "answer": "認める",    "options": ["認める", "確保する", "成し遂げる", "割り当てる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 150,    "question": "individual",    "answer": "個人の",    "options": ["金銭上の", "個人の", "付加的な", "晴れた"]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 151,    "question": "contribute",    "answer": "貢献する",    "options": ["利益を得る", "貢献する", "検討する", "通勤する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 152,    "question": "budget",    "answer": "予算",    "options": ["科目", "節約", "機器", "予算"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 153,    "question": "allow",    "answer": "許す",    "options": ["許す", "荷物を積む", "予期する", "稼ぐ"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 154,    "question": "demonstrate",    "answer": "実演する",    "options": ["再開する", "参照する", "実演する", "告白する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 155,    "question": "exchange",    "answer": "交換する",    "options": ["交換する", "資金を与える", "確認する", "旅行する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 156,    "question": "application",    "answer": "応募",    "options": ["手に入ること", "詳細", "応募", "費用"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 157,    "question": "survey",    "answer": "調査",    "options": ["会議", "実験", "調査", "開くこと"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 158,    "question": "obey",    "answer": "従う",    "options": ["みなす", "従う", "尋ねる", "破壊する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 159,    "question": "reward",    "answer": "報酬",    "options": ["報酬", "展示", "社員", "善意の行為"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 160,    "question": "prefer",    "answer": "の方を好む",    "options": ["のせいにする", "もうかる", "取り除く", "の方を好む"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 161,    "question": "contract",    "answer": "契約",    "options": ["決定", "成長", "契約", "利益"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 162,    "question": "agency",    "answer": "代理店",    "options": ["予約", "活動", "応募", "代理店"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 163,    "question": "release",    "answer": "発表する",    "options": ["主演する", "接続する", "発表する", "往復運転で運ぶ"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 164,    "question": "management",    "answer": "経営",    "options": ["配達", "結果", "経営", "社員"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 165,    "question": "financial",    "answer": "金銭上の",    "options": ["地元の", "入手できる", "金銭上の", "個人の"]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 166,    "question": "relax",    "answer": "ゆるめる",    "options": ["許す", "申し出る", "届ける", "ゆるめる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 167,    "question": "profitable",    "answer": "もうかる",    "options": ["制定する", "注ぐ", "もうかる", "貢献する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 168,    "question": "hire",    "answer": "雇う",    "options": ["解雇する", "向ける", "雇う", "ひきつける"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 169,    "question": "performance",    "answer": "業績",    "options": ["労働", "業績", "研究", "学位"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 170,    "question": "charge",    "answer": "充電する",    "options": ["満足させる", "占有する", "取り戻す", "充電する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 171,    "question": "graduate",    "answer": "卒業する",    "options": ["実行する", "貢献する", "交換する", "卒業する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 172,    "question": "reschedule",    "answer": "予定を変更する",    "options": ["出発する", "修正する", "", "予定を変更する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 173,    "question": "postpone",    "answer": "延期する",    "options": ["延期する", "再開する", "指示する", "実演する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 174,    "question": "pleased",    "answer": "喜んで",    "options": ["喜んで", "付加的な", "気前のよい", "晴れた"]  ,"part": "adjective"},
{    "number": 175,    "question": "argue",    "answer": "議論する",    "options": ["説明する", "議論する", "雇う", "主催する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 176,    "question": "lead",    "answer": "導く",    "options": ["導く", "更新する", "設立する", "荷物を積む"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 177,    "question": "document",    "answer": "記録する",    "options": ["記録する", "検討する", "修理する", "維持する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 178,    "question": "confirm",    "answer": "確認する",    "options": ["追及する", "解雇する", "確認する", "挨拶する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 179,    "question": "illustrate",    "answer": "説明する",    "options": ["往復運転で運ぶ", "見逃す", "説明する", "推薦する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 180,    "question": "recommend",    "answer": "推薦する",    "options": ["増える", "成し遂げる", "認める", "推薦する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 181,    "question": "award",    "answer": "賞",    "options": ["学位", "量", "伝統", "賞"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 182,    "question": "examine",    "answer": "詳しく調べる",    "options": ["詳しく調べる", "ゆるめる", "掃く", "割り当てる"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 183,    "question": "propose",    "answer": "提案する",    "options": ["確保する", "提案する", "現れる", "餌を与える"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 184,    "question": "clothing",    "answer": "衣類",    "options": ["衣類", "関係", "費用", "代理店"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 185,    "question": "carry",    "answer": "運ぶ",    "options": ["輸入する", "運ぶ", "積み重ねる", "引き起こす"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 186,    "question": "display",    "answer": "展示",    "options": ["展示", "顧客", "商品", "売り場"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 187,    "question": "conduct",    "answer": "実行する",    "options": ["集中させる", "実行する", "もてなす", "往復運転で運ぶ"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 188,    "question": "represent",    "answer": "代表する",    "options": ["おわびをする", "稼ぐ", "代表する", "の方を好む"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 189,    "question": "candidate",    "answer": "候補者",    "options": ["労働力", "施設", "広告", "候補者"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 190,    "question": "exclude",    "answer": "除く",    "options": ["移す", "貢献する", "取り替える", "除く"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 191,    "question": "possess",    "answer": "所有する",    "options": ["延期する", "維持する", "所有する", "提供する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 192,    "question": "exhibit",    "answer": "展示物",    "options": ["配達", "結果", "注意", "展示物"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 193,    "question": "invest",    "answer": "投資する",    "options": ["申し出る", "知らせる", "分析する", "投資する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 194,    "question": "overlook",    "answer": "見逃す",    "options": ["修正する", "空にする", "予定を変更する", "見逃す"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 195,    "question": "session",    "answer": "集まり",    "options": ["商品", "科目", "収入", "集まり"]  ,"part": "noun"},
{    "number": 196,    "question": "purchase",    "answer": "購入する",    "options": ["見て回る", "購入する", "もうかる", "資金を与える"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 197,    "question": "transform",    "answer": "変える",    "options": ["充電する", "変える", "却下する", "比較する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 198,    "question": "note",    "answer": "述べる",    "options": ["述べる", "拒む", "主演する", "発表する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 199,    "question": "ship",    "answer": "出荷する",    "options": ["破壊する", "荷物を積む", "郵送する", "出荷する"]  ,"part": "verb"},
{    "number": 200,    "question": "dispute",   "answer": "異議を唱える","options": ["予定を変更する", "餌を与える", "往復運転で運ぶ", "異議を唱える"],"part": "verb"},
]
